Contact

mjennifer.hufstedler@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mary-jenniferhufstedler-bsn-cnor-5a870290 (Linkedln)

Top Skills

Healthcare Surgical Oncology Trauma Surgery

Mary Jennifer Hufstedler BSN,CNOR

Clinical Nurse-Operating Room at UT MD Anderson Cancer Center - Cancer Prevention Research Training Program

Richmond, Texas

Summary

Experienced Clinical Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Peri-Operative, Medical-Surgical, CNOR, Life Support, and Surgical Oncology. Strong healthcare services professional presently focused in Pursuing a Degree in MSN Leadership and Management from Walden University.

Experience

UT MD Anderson Cancer Center - Cancer Prevention Research
Training Program
Operating Room Nurse
October 2014 - Present (5 years 8 months)
Houston, Texas Area

Memorial Hermann Health System Clinical Nurse April 2014 - December 2014 (9 months) Houston, Texas Area

Regional One Health

7 years 10 months

Patient Care Coordinator, Trauma Operating Room November 2011 - April 2014 (2 years 6 months) Memphis Tn

Functions as a charge nurse running the OR schedule. Coordinates care with other members of the Trauma Team to ensure smooth operation of a busy Trauma OR. Other responsibilities include staff scheduling, monitoring OR Delays, Implant Tracking, and payroll.

Staff Nurse
July 2006 - April 2014 (7 years 10 months)
Page 1 of 2

St. Jude Children's Research Hospital Clinical Nurse April 2005 - June 2006 (1 year 3 months) Greater Memphis Area

Children's National Health System
Clinical Nurse II
June 2003 - March 2005 (1 year 10 months)
Washington D.C. Metro Area

MedStar Georgetown University Hospital Clinical Nurse 1 January 2003 - October 2003 (10 months) Washington, District Of Columbia

Hickory House Nursing Home Nurse Supervisor March 2001 - January 2003 (1 year 11 months) Honey Brook, Pennsylvania

West Visayas State University Medical Center Staff Registered Nurse- Operating Room June 1996 - February 2001 (4 years 9 months) Iloilo City, Philippines

Education

Walden University
Student, Pursuing a Degree in MSN Leadership and
Management · (2017 - 2020)

West Visayas State University
Bachelor's degree, Nursing Education · (1991 - 1995)